[
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "一",
    "options": [
      "fire",
      "five",
      "one",
      "down"
    ],
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "two",
    "options": [
      "上",
      "母",
      "二",
      "万"
    ],
    "answer": "二"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "三",
    "options": [
      "ten thousand",
      "ear",
      "eye",
      "three"
    ],
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "four",
    "options": [
      "四",
      "母",
      "食",
      "口"
    ],
    "answer": "四"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "五",
    "options": [
      "drink",
      "five",
      "one",
      "mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "six",
    "options": [
      "時",
      "上",
      "目",
      "六"
    ],
    "answer": "六"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "七",
    "options": [
      "enter",
      "before",
      "seven",
      "minute"
    ],
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "eight",
    "options": [
      "早",
      "何",
      "左",
      "八"
    ],
    "answer": "八"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "九",
    "options": [
      "after",
      "rain",
      "woman",
      "nine"
    ],
    "answer": "nine"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "ten",
    "options": [
      "耳",
      "千",
      "木",
      "十"
    ],
    "answer": "十"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "百",
    "options": [
      "mountain",
      "hundred",
      "hear",
      "after"
    ],
    "answer": "hundred"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "thousand",
    "options": [
      "入",
      "千",
      "十",
      "天"
    ],
    "answer": "千"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "万",
    "options": [
      "mountain",
      "ten thousand",
      "early",
      "school"
    ],
    "answer": "ten thousand"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "yen",
    "options": [
      "耳",
      "八",
      "月",
      "円"
    ],
    "answer": "円"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "上",
    "options": [
      "eye",
      "heaven",
      "up",
      "nine"
    ],
    "answer": "up"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "down",
    "options": [
      "見",
      "大",
      "下",
      "聞"
    ],
    "answer": "下"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "左",
    "options": [
      "left",
      "white",
      "what",
      "spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "left"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "right",
    "options": [
      "後",
      "口",
      "右",
      "中"
    ],
    "answer": "右"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "中",
    "options": [
      "up",
      "middle",
      "small",
      "mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "middle"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "big",
    "options": [
      "大",
      "今",
      "早",
      "休"
    ],
    "answer": "大"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "小",
    "options": [
      "small",
      "father",
      "up",
      "two"
    ],
    "answer": "small"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "mountain",
    "options": [
      "木",
      "山",
      "話",
      "上"
    ],
    "answer": "山"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "川",
    "options": [
      "rice field",
      "spirit",
      "name",
      "river"
    ],
    "answer": "river"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "rice field",
    "options": [
      "入",
      "田",
      "男",
      "名"
    ],
    "answer": "田"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "人",
    "options": [
      "one",
      "person",
      "mother",
      "electricity"
    ],
    "answer": "person"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "woman",
    "options": [
      "土",
      "後",
      "女",
      "上"
    ],
    "answer": "女"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "男",
    "options": [
      "sky",
      "life",
      "hundred",
      "man"
    ],
    "answer": "man"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "child",
    "options": [
      "子",
      "学",
      "父",
      "左"
    ],
    "answer": "子"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "目",
    "options": [
      "eye",
      "woman",
      "child",
      "mother"
    ],
    "answer": "eye"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "mouth",
    "options": [
      "読",
      "車",
      "書",
      "口"
    ],
    "answer": "口"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "耳",
    "options": [
      "three",
      "ear",
      "time",
      "nine"
    ],
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "hand",
    "options": [
      "八",
      "十",
      "手",
      "一"
    ],
    "answer": "手"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "足",
    "options": [
      "foot",
      "ten",
      "house",
      "year"
    ],
    "answer": "foot"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "power",
    "options": [
      "母",
      "子",
      "力",
      "左"
    ],
    "answer": "力"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "気",
    "options": [
      "ten thousand",
      "come",
      "person",
      "spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "spirit"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "heaven",
    "options": [
      "前",
      "天",
      "飲",
      "来"
    ],
    "answer": "天"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "火",
    "options": [
      "ten thousand",
      "go",
      "fire",
      "eight"
    ],
    "answer": "fire"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "water",
    "options": [
      "何",
      "水",
      "書",
      "人"
    ],
    "answer": "水"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "木",
    "options": [
      "school",
      "hand",
      "heaven",
      "tree"
    ],
    "answer": "tree"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "gold",
    "options": [
      "七",
      "母",
      "二",
      "金"
    ],
    "answer": "金"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "土",
    "options": [
      "life",
      "earth",
      "previous",
      "come"
    ],
    "answer": "earth"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "sun",
    "options": [
      "日",
      "早",
      "山",
      "一"
    ],
    "answer": "日"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "月",
    "options": [
      "fire",
      "drink",
      "moon",
      "white"
    ],
    "answer": "moon"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "year",
    "options": [
      "八",
      "水",
      "子",
      "年"
    ],
    "answer": "年"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "時",
    "options": [
      "eight",
      "time",
      "seven",
      "shop"
    ],
    "answer": "time"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "minute",
    "options": [
      "百",
      "家",
      "分",
      "八"
    ],
    "answer": "分"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "前",
    "options": [
      "down",
      "before",
      "go",
      "ear"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "after",
    "options": [
      "店",
      "後",
      "百",
      "食"
    ],
    "answer": "後"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "午",
    "options": [
      "ear",
      "earth",
      "noon",
      "power"
    ],
    "answer": "noon"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "early",
    "options": [
      "土",
      "十",
      "聞",
      "早"
    ],
    "answer": "早"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "今",
    "options": [
      "child",
      "ten",
      "now",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "now"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "see",
    "options": [
      "後",
      "九",
      "見",
      "手"
    ],
    "answer": "見"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "行",
    "options": [
      "exit",
      "mother",
      "tree",
      "go"
    ],
    "answer": "go"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "come",
    "options": [
      "円",
      "右",
      "力",
      "来"
    ],
    "answer": "来"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "食",
    "options": [
      "eat",
      "enter",
      "fire",
      "spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "eat"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "drink",
    "options": [
      "力",
      "飲",
      "男",
      "名"
    ],
    "answer": "飲"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "話",
    "options": [
      "eat",
      "thousand",
      "heaven",
      "talk"
    ],
    "answer": "talk"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "read",
    "options": [
      "読",
      "左",
      "力",
      "小"
    ],
    "answer": "読"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "書",
    "options": [
      "white",
      "up",
      "two",
      "write"
    ],
    "answer": "write"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "hear",
    "options": [
      "五",
      "聞",
      "後",
      "母"
    ],
    "answer": "聞"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "校",
    "options": [
      "gold",
      "before",
      "six",
      "school"
    ],
    "answer": "school"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "study",
    "options": [
      "手",
      "学",
      "円",
      "分"
    ],
    "answer": "学"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "先",
    "options": [
      "ear",
      "small",
      "previous",
      "river"
    ],
    "answer": "previous"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "life",
    "options": [
      "月",
      "手",
      "生",
      "行"
    ],
    "answer": "生"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "友",
    "options": [
      "five",
      "school",
      "friend",
      "noon"
    ],
    "answer": "friend"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "name",
    "options": [
      "口",
      "金",
      "名",
      "時"
    ],
    "answer": "名"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "家",
    "options": [
      "heaven",
      "moon",
      "see",
      "house"
    ],
    "answer": "house"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "car",
    "options": [
      "名",
      "何",
      "車",
      "見"
    ],
    "answer": "車"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "電",
    "options": [
      "power",
      "shop",
      "electricity",
      "river"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "what",
    "options": [
      "時",
      "何",
      "休",
      "飲"
    ],
    "answer": "何"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "母",
    "options": [
      "person",
      "early",
      "mother",
      "rain"
    ],
    "answer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "father",
    "options": [
      "父",
      "家",
      "電",
      "一"
    ],
    "answer": "父"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "白",
    "options": [
      "earth",
      "nine",
      "moon",
      "white"
    ],
    "answer": "white"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "sky",
    "options": [
      "空",
      "行",
      "友",
      "金"
    ],
    "answer": "空"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "雨",
    "options": [
      "rain",
      "mother",
      "left",
      "person"
    ],
    "answer": "rain"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "shop",
    "options": [
      "白",
      "店",
      "川",
      "出"
    ],
    "answer": "店"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "会",
    "options": [
      "meet",
      "tree",
      "fire",
      "man"
    ],
    "answer": "meet"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "rest",
    "options": [
      "聞",
      "休",
      "話",
      "子"
    ],
    "answer": "休"
  },
  {
    "type": "kanji-to-meaning",
    "question": "入",
    "options": [
      "hundred",
      "name",
      "enter",
      "fire"
    ],
    "answer": "enter"
  },
  {
    "type": "meaning-to-kanji",
    "question": "exit",
    "options": [
      "女",
      "目",
      "出",
      "金"
    ],
    "answer": "出"
  }
]
